Bernard L. Fontana Papers 1832-2000 (bulk 1956-1985)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Bernard Fontana Papers 1832-2000 (bulk 1965-1985)
Bernard Fontana Papers
MS 434
Fontana, Bernard L.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://www.library.arizona.edu/speccoll
This collection contains materials relating to Bernard (Bunny) Fontana, a prominent anthropologist and active community member in Southern Arizona. Materials include activity files, which include documentation of activities in organizations, speeches, conferences, and research; writings, which include manuscripts and book reviews. Also included is correspondence, personal files and oversize materials.
52.5 linear feet
Restrictions
None
Accruals
Further accurrals are anticipated
Materials pertaining to Fontana’s work as an ethnologist for the Arizona State Museum can be found at the Arizona State Museum Library. Bunny's work with Patronato San Xavier Collection (MS 459), and Southwest Mission Research Center records (MS 443) are held by University of Arizona Library Special Collections.
Biographical Note
Bernard (Bunny) Lee Fontana was a prominent anthropologist based out of the University of Arizona. He participated in many activities around Sonora and southern Arizona and was also a prolific author who preferred to be known as Bunny.
Bunny Fontana was born January 7, 1931 in Oakland, California. He attended the University of California at Berkeley where he earned his B.A. in Anthropology in 1953. He married his high school sweetheart, Hazel Ann McFeely, on June 27, 1954. From 1953-1955 Bunny served in the United States Army where he was briefly stationed in Alaska. Upon discharge from the military he attended the University of Arizona where he earned his Ph.D. in anthropology in 1960. Bunny and Hazel started their family in 1962 with the birth of son Geoffrey. Nicholas followed in 1965, and Francesca arrived in 1968.
Bunny held the positions of field historian in the University of Arizona Library, ethnologist in the Arizona State Museum, and lecturer in the Department of Anthropology. He was very active professionally and wrote many articles, books, and other literary contributions. He was also an editor, active community member, lecturer and private consultant.
Among his contributions are the books: A Gift of Angels: The Art of Mission San Xavier del Bac; Trails to Tiburón: The 1894 and 1895 Field Diaries of W J McGee; Tarahumara: Where Night is the Day of the Moon and Of Earth and Little Rain: The Papago Indians. Bunny Fontana was very involved in Tohono O’odham affairs as he and his wife lived extremely close to the Tohono O’odham reservation near the San Xavier del Bac Mission in Tucson, Arizona. Fontana’s main research interest was Southwest ethnohistory, history and ethnology, including the Mexican states of Sonora and Chihuahua. He was a member of Patronato San Xavier which is dedicated to preserving and promoting the Mission of San Xavier del Bac. Bunny’s interest in mission history also aided him in his work as field historian in which he traveled to all areas of Arizona and Sonora and augmented the holdings of the University of Arizona’s Special Collections.
Bunny retired from the University of Arizona in 1992 and Hazel Fontana passed away in February 2009. Bunny Fontana remaines active in organizations and continues attending meetings, conferences, and writing articles and book reviews.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 5 series.
Series I: Activity Files, 1859-2000
Series II: Writings, 1832-1999 1832-1999
Series III: Correspondence, 1920-2000
Series IV:Personal Files, 1956-1992
Series V: Oversize, 1952-1991
Scope and Content Note
Papers, 1832-2000 (bulk 1965-1985). This collection contains the papers of Bernard (Bunny) Fontana documenting his scholarly, professional and community involvement. The bulk of the materials are activity files which document his activity with organizations, projects, research and speeches. Included in these files are communications, informational research materials, photographs and talks. Also included are writings such as manuscripts written by Fontana and others as well as book reviews and student writings. In addition there are correspondence files which are arranged in their original filing scheme, personal files, and oversize materials.
Access Terms
Fontana, Bernard L.
University of Arizona. Library. Special Collections
University of Arizona
Sonora (Mexico: State) - History
Tucson (Ariz.) - History
Mission San Xavier del Bac (Tucson, Ariz.)
Tohono O'Odham Indians.
Missions--Arizona--History.
Missions-- Mexico -- Sonora (State).
Patronato San Xavier.
Southwestern Mission Research Center (U.S.)
Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum (Tucson, Ariz.)
Container List
- Series I: Activity Files, 1859-2000
  Alphabetical. This series contains documentation of Bunny Fontana’s professional activities. It is divided into four subseries.
  Subseries 1: Organizations: Contains documents relating to activities with organizations.
  Subseries 2: Projects and Research: Contains research documents and information on the planning of projects.
  Subseries 3: Conferences: Contains conference programs and communication.
  Subseries 4: Speeches and Talk: Contains presented talks and speeches.
  - Subseries 1: Organizations
    - Speeches and Talk: Contains presented talks and speeches., 1958-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Association for State and Local History., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Indian Scholars Convention., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American Society for Ethnohistory – Annual Meeting Programs., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - American Society for Ethnohistory – Correspondence., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - American Society for Ethnohistory – Correspondence., 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - American Society for Ethnohistory – Henry F. Dobyns., 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - American Society for Ethnohistory – Meeting., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - American Society for Ethnohistory – Meeting., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - American Society for Ethnohistory – Nominations., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - American Studies Association., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The American Way – Correspondence A-L., 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - The American Way – Correspondence M-Z., undated; 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The American Way – Native American Articles., 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Arizona Archaeological and Historical Society – Newsletters., 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Arizona Archaeological and Historical Society – Newsletters., 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Arizona Archaeological and Historical Society – Newsletters., 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Arizona Center for the Book., undated; 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Arizona Daily Star Southwest Book Selections., 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Arizona Historical Society – 1960 Tucson Convention., undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Arizona Historical Society – 1963 Tucson Convention., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Arizona Historical Society – 1972 and 1974 Conventions., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Arizona Historical Society – 1976 Flagstaff Convention., undated; 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Arizona Historical Society – 1977 Convention., undated; 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Arizona Historical Society – 1977 Convention. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Arizona Historical Society – 1978 Ft. Huachuca Convention., undated; 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Arizona Historical Society – Board of Directors., undated; 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Arizona Historical Society – Board of Directors., undated; 1979 (Box 2, 1)
    - Arizona Historical Society – Board of Directors., undated; 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Arizona Historical Society – Convention Committee., undated; 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Arizona Historical Society – Executive Committee., undated; 1972-1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Arizona Historical Society – General., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Arizona Historical Society – Liaisons., undated; 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Arizona Historical Society – Policy and Planning Committee., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Arizona Historical Society – Preservation Committee., undated; 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Arizona Press Women., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - American Society for Ethnography., undated; 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Board of Directors., 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Board of Directors., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Board of Directors., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Board of Directors., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Board of Directors., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Board of Directors., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Board of Directors., 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Board of Trustees Meetings., 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Committees., undated; 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Docents., undated; 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Fiscal Matters., 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Fiscal Matters., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – General., undated; 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – George L. Mountain Lion Club., 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Gift Shop Committee., 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Governing Documents., undated; 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Hal Gras., 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Inge Poglayen, undated; 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Large Animal Habitat., undated; 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Meeting Minutes., 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Newsletters., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Newsletters., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Newsletters., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Newsletters., 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Newsletters., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Nominations Committee., 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – “People in the Desert”., 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Personnel Issues., 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Policy Review., 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Research Committee., undated; 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum – Spanish Names of Animals., undated; 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation – “The Paradise Land”., undated; 1978-1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Bureau of Land Management – Columbus Quincentenary Meeting., undated; 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Bureau of Land Management – San Pedro River., undated; 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Bureau of Land Management – San Pedro River., undated; 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Cabeza Prieta National Wildlife Refuge 50th Anniversary., 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - CALI Conference., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - California Mission Studies Association., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - City of Tucson – Affirmative Action Workshop., undated; 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Cochise Quarterly Newsletter., undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Coronado International Monument Commission., undated; 1937-1947 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Coronado International Monument Commission., 1948-1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Council for Museum Anthropology., 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Crow Canyon Archaeological Center - Fall 1993 Tours., undated; 1971-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Crow Canyon Archaeological Center – Field Seminar., 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Crow Canyon Archaeological Center – Field Seminar., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Crow Canyon Archaeological Center – Field Seminar Planning., undated; 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - DeGolyer Library Quincentenary., 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - DeGrazia Foundation., 1977-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Economic Development Administration., 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Education Expeditions International – Proposals., undated; 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - El Paso Museum of History., 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Ford Foundation – Grant Proposal., undated; 1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Goals for Tucson., undated; 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Hispanic Culture Foundation. undated, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Journal of Arid Environments., undated; 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Journal of the Southwest Editorial Board., 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Kino Tercentennial Committee – Miscellaneous., 1983-1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Kino Tercentennial Committee – Newspaper Coverage., 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Library Humanities Grant Application., 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Museum of New Mexico – Columbus Quincentenary., undated; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Museum of New Mexico – NEH Planning Consultant., undated; 1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Museum of New Mexico – NEH Planning Consultant., 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Museum of New Mexico – Palace of the Governors Exhibit (1 of 2)., 1991 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Museum of New Mexico – Palace of the Governors Exhibit (2 of 2)., 1991 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Museum of New Mexico – Segesserltide Paintings., undated; 1963-1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The National Heritage Trust., undated; 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - National Park Service – Arizona Archaeological Center., undated; 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - National Park Service – Arizona Archaeological Center., 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - National Park Service – Coronado National Memorial., undated; 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - National Park Service – Coronado National Memorial Planning., undated; 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - National Park Service – Coronado Pageants and Correspondence, undated; 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - National Park Service – Ft. Bowie Historical Site., 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - National Park Service – Grand Canyon Feral Burro Control., 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - National Park Service – Grand Canyon Information., undated; 1959-1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - National Park Service – Grand Canyon News., 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - National Park Service – Grand Canyon River Planning., 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - National Park Service – Lake Mead Development., undated; 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - National Park Service – Lake Mead Hearings., undated; 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - National Park Service – Park Information., 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - National Park Service – Secret Mountain., undated; 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association., undated; 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - National Register of Historic Places., 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Northland Press., 1975-1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - North/South Cultural Center., undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - One World Journeys – Desert Trek., 2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Papago Press., 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Arizona Heritage Alliance, Inc., 1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Awards., 1998 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Bicentennial Celebration Planning., 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Patronato San Xavier – City of Tucson Proclamation., 1997 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Getty Grant Annotated Bibliography., 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Information Sheets., 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Kress Foundation., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Lazzarini Visit and Analysis., 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Lightning Protection., 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Meeting Minutes., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Meeting Minutes., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Meeting Minutes., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Mold Resume., undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Patronato San Xavier – National Park Service Grant., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Quatrefoil Windows (Vint)., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Schwartzbaum Proposals., 1990-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Secretary’s File., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Secretary’s File., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Secretary’s File (1 of 2)., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Secretary’s File (2 of 2)., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Secretary’s File., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Talks Given., 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Talks Given., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Talks Given., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Tucson Museum of Art Exhibit., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Vint’s Architectural Field Reports., 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Patronato San Xavier – Vint’s Vestibule Proposal., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Scarecrow Press., 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Society for American Archaeology., undated; 1962 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Society for American Archaeology., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – A-E., 1967-1970 (Box 7, type= "folder"1)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – Charles H. Fairbanks., 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – General., 1967-1971 (Box 7, 3)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – John L. Cutter., 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – Kansas City Conference., undated; 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – Stanley South., 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – Symposium on Spanish Colonial., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – T-V., 1964-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Society for Historical Archaeology – W-Z., 1962-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Buford Pickens Study of Kino Missions – Correspondence., 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Buford Pickens Study of Kino Missions – Buford Pickens Study of Kino Missions – Draft 2., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Buford Pickens Study of Kino Missions – Manuscript., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – Correspondence., undated; 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – General., undated; 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – Manuscript 1 (1 of 2)., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – Manuscript 2 (2 of 2)., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – Manuscript 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – Manuscript Draft., undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – Manuscript Reviews., undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – References Cited., undated; 1951-1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Federico Ronstadt – Substituted Manuscript Pages., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Frederick Hodge., 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Hancock/Yetman “Visions of Sonora”., undated; 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – Information., 1980-1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Southwest Center – Book Series – J.P.S. Brown “The Faces of Sonora”., undated; 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Southwest Center – General., undated; 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Southwest Center – General., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Southwest Center – General., 1990-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Center – Planning., undated; 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Southwest Center – Search for New Director., undated; 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Southwest Environmental Services., undated; 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Southwest Folklore Center., undated; 1978-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Southwestern Library Association., undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Southwestern Library Association., 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – Correspondence And Proposals., 1966-1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – Correspondence And Proposals., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – Correspondence And Proposals., 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – Governing Documents., 1965-1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – Historical Summaries., undated; 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – Mission Tours., 1956-1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – Mission Tours., 1988-1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – Santa Cruz Valley Tour., undated; 1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Southwestern Mission Research Center – St. Michael’s Mission., 1961-1985 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - St. Michael’s Press., 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Time-Life Books – The Gamblers., 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Tucson Corral of the Westerners., undated; 1976-1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Tucson Historical Committee., 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Tucson Historical Committee., 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Tucson Public Library – Sonoran Heritage Program (1 of 2)., undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Tucson Public Library – Sonoran Heritage Program (2 of 2)., undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Tucson Public Library – Sonoran Heritage Program., 1969-1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - UCLA Archaeology., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - University of Arizona – Amerind Club., unidate; 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - University of Arizona – Arizona State Museum., undated; 1963-1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - University of Arizona – Arizona Quarterly., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - University of Arizona – Centennial Celebration., undated; 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - University of Arizona – Columbus Quincentennial., undated; 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - University of Arizona – Columbus Quincentennial., 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - University of Arizona – Committee on Minority Salary Equity., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - University of Arizona – Community Development., undated; 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - University of Arizona – Folklore Committee., undated; 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - University of Arizona – Friends of the Library – Ann-Eve Mansfeld Johnson Memorial Fund., 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - University of Arizona – Friends of the Library – Acquisitions., undated; 1984-1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - University of Arizona – Friends of the Library – Acquisitions Through Estates., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)